Guide to the Historical Planning publications collection, 1888-2002.
Historical Planning publications collection
- Series V. Housing
  - Housing - U.S. - Oregon, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Housing - U.S. - Pennsylvania - Philadelphia, 1950-1960 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Housing - U.S. - Pennsylvania - Philadelphia Pittsburgh, 1930-1950 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Housing - U.S. - Pennsylvania - Misc.Cities, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Housing - U.S. - Pennsylvania - Misc.Cities, 1910, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Housing - U.S. - Phode Island Providence, 1950-1960 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Housing - U.S. - Tennessee - Knoxville, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Housing - U.S. - Tennessee - Memphis, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Housing - U.S. - Tennessee - Misc Cities, 1940-1950 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Housing - U.S. - Texas - Fortworth, 1930-1940 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Housing - U.S. - Texas, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Housing - U.S. - Virginia - Miscellaneous, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Housing - U.S. - Virginia - Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Housing - U.S. - Virginia - Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Housing - U.S. - Washington - Seattle, 1940-1960 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Housing - U.S. - Washington - Misc, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Housing - U.S. - Virginia - Norfolk, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Housing - U.S. - Washington, D.C, 1950-1960 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Housing - U.S. - Wisconsin, 1930-1940 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Housing - U.S. - Puerto Rico, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Housing - Housing? (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes General, 1930-1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes - Illinois, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Housing - Administration, 1940, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Housing - Administration New York - Ithaca, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Housing - Aged, 1950-1960 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Housing - Aged, 1950-1960 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Housing - Aged, 1930, 1940-1950 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Housing - Aged, 1950-1960 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Housing - Defense Workers, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Housing - Defense Workers, 1940-1950 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Housing - Foreign - General, 1936-1957 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Housing - Foreign - Asia, 1950-1958 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Housing - Foreign - Australia, 1966-1968 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Housing - Foreign - Austria, 1923-1926 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Housing - Foreign - Borneo, 1962-1967 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Housing - Foreign - Brazil, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Housing - Foreign - British African Territory, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Housing - Foreign - British Honduras, 1955-1960 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Housing - Foreign - Burma, 1952-1957 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Housing - Foreign - Canada (1), 1944-1955 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Housing - Foreign - Canada (2), 1956-1971 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Housing - Foreign - Chile, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Housing - Foreign - Columbia, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Housing - Foreign - Cyprus, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Housing - Foreign - Denmark, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Housing - Foreign - Europe, 1936-1953 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Housing - Foreign - France (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Housing - Foreign - Germany, 1950-1956 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Housing - Foreign - Great Britain (1), 1920-1939 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Housing - Foreign - Great Britain (2), 1945-1959 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Housing - Foreign - Great Britain (3), 1960-1966 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Housing - Foreign - Great Britain - Leeds (Oversized) (Box 69)
- Series VI. Industries
  - Industries - U.S. - Florida, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Industries - Sites - General, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Industries - General, 1940-1950 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Industries - General, 1940-1951 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Industries - Location, 1940-1952 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Industries - Sites - Illinois, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Industries - Sites - Maryland (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Industries - Sites - Michigan, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Industries - Sites - New York, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Industries - Sites - New York, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Industries - Sites - Ohio, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Industries - Sites - North Carolina (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Industries - Sites - West Virginia (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Industries - U.S - Arizona, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Industries - U.S - Arkansas, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Industries - U.S - California, 1940-1950 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Industries - U.S - California, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Industries - U.S - California, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Industries - U.S - Connecticut, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Industries - U.S - Florida (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Industries - U.S - Florida, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Industries - U.S - Georgia, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Industries - U.S - Kansas, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Industries - U.S. - Kansas - Manhattan (Oversized), 1965 (Box 69)
  - Industries - U.S - Kentucky, 1950-1960 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Industries - U.S - Maryland, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Industries - U.S - Massachusetts, 1940-1950 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Industries - U.S - Illinois, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Industries - U.S - Maine (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Industries - U.S - Michigan, 1940-1950 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Industries - U.S - Michigan, 1950-1960 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Industries - U.S - Missouri, 1940-1950 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Industries - U.S - New Jersey, 1950-1960 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Industries - U.S - New York, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Industries - U.S - New York, 1940-1950 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Industries - U.S - New York, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Industries - U.S - New York, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Industries - U.S - New York, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Industries - U.S - New York, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Industries - U.S - New York, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Industries - U.S - New York (Oversized) (Box 61)
  - Industries - U.S. - New York (Oversized), 1944 (Box 69)
  - Industries - U.S - North Carolina, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Industries - U.S. - Ohio, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Industries - U.S. - Oklahoma, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Industries - U.S. - Oregon, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Industries - U.S. - Pacific Northwest, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Industries - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Industries - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Industries - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1940-1960 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Industries - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Industries - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Industries - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1910,1950-1960 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Industries - U.S. - Rhode Island, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Industries - U.S. - South Carolina, 1920-1940 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Industries - U.S. - South Carolina, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Industries - U.S. - South Dakota, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Industries - U.S. - Tennessee, 1940,1960 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Industries - TVA, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Industries - U.S. - Texas, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Industries - U.S. - Vermont, 1940-1950 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Industries - U.S. - Virginia, 2959 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Industries - U.S. - Washington, 1950-1960 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Industries - U.S. - West Virginia, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Industries - U.S. - Wisconsin, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Industries - Foreign - Canada, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Industries - Foreign - Canada, 1950-1960 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Industries - Foreign - Great Britain, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Series VII. Land - Use, Values
  - Land Use - U.S. - Florida - Broward County (Oversized), 1985 (Box 69)
  - Land Use - U.S.- Michigan (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Comparative Land Area Tabulations. South Oakland Development Area -4A-, September 1, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Detroit Metropolitan Area Regional Planning Commission
    - Land Use Plan for the Detroit Region, August 1, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Detroit Metropolitan Area Regional Planning Commission, 2 copies
    - Land Use Plan (Map), June 27, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1958 Land Use In the Detroit Region., August 1, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Comparative Land Area Tabulations. South Macomb Development Area -1A-, August 1, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Land Use - U.S.- Michigan (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - The Michigan Program of Land Use Planning and the Removal of Marginal Agricultural Land From Production (Box 1, Folder 2)
      E.L. Anthony, College of Agriculture, Michigan State College, et al.
    - Existing Land Use and Circulation in Sault Ste. Marie, November 1, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Richard P. Duke, Institute for Community Development, Michigan State University
    - A Diagnosis and Suggested Treatment of an Urban Community's Land Problems (Flint, Michigan), February 1, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Edmund N. Bacon, Reprinted from The Journal of Land Public Utility Economics, With A Supplement Consisting of Three Neighborhood Studies
    - Land Use 1958. Survey and Inventory- Saginaw and Environs, October 1, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Russel O. Koenig and Cleve M. Orler
    - Land and People of St. Clair County. 1951., January 1, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      St. Clair County Planning Commission
  - Land Use - Michigan - Detroit` (Oversized), 1946 (Box 70)
  - Land Use - U.S. - Missouri - St. Louis (Oversized), 1956 (Box 70)
  - Land Use - U.S.- Montana (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Land Use Adjustment in the Buffalo Creek Grazing District. Yellowstone, Montana., August 1, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      James H. Marshall, Stanley W. Voelker, U.S. Department of Agriculture
  - Land Use - U.S.- New Jersey (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Land Use Plan for the Meadowlands. East Rutherford, N.J. Master Plan Report 1., September 1, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Passaic-Bergen Community Planning Association
    - Borough of Fair Lawn Master Plan Studies. Land Use. Population. Traffic. Education. Recreation. Utilities., October 1, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Community Planning Associates, Inc.
  - Land Use - U.S.- New Jersey (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Franklin Township Master Plan Report No. 1, December 1, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      New Jersey State Department of Conservation and Economic Development
    - City of Long Branch Master Plan Report Number 1. Land Use., December 1, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Land Use - U.S.- New Jersey (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Future Development In Bergen County, April 1, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      County of Bergen N.J. Planning Board
    - Townscape - Patterns of Land Unused. ( A Preliminary Report on Land Unused in Ocean Township, New Jersey), July 1, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Community Housing and Planning Associates
    - Land Use Report for Monmouth Coastal Region, June 27, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Monmouth County Planning Board
  - Land Use - U.S.- New Jersey (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Randolph Township, N.J. Survey of Land Use and Zoning., March 1, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Report on Land Use. (City of Paterson, N.J.), November 1, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Paterson Planning Board
    - Living Space for a Million People (Passaic County, N.J.), ca. 1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Passaic County Planning Board.
    - The Port Authority Review., January 1, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Vol. 2, No. 2
  - Land Use - U.S.- New Mexico (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Land Use Plan- 1985. Albuquerque, New Mexico., February 1, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      City of Albuquerque Planning Department. One insert.
  - Land Use - U.S.- New York (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Land Use Survey and Analysis. Camillus, New York., May 20, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Arthur Reed
    - Land Use Problem In New York State, August 1, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      New York State College of Agriculture, Department of Agricultural Economics and Farm Management
    - New York State Land Use and Natural Resources Inventory. Pilot Study. Technical Manual., October 1, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Ronald Shelton, Center for Aerial Photographic Studies, Cornell University
  - Land Use - U.S.- New York (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Land Use and Community Taxes. A Planning Program for the Northeast Section of Yorktown, N.Y. Report Number 1., December 1, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Frederick P. Clarke and Associates
    - Northeast Land Use Plan. A Planning Program for the Northeast Section of Yorktown, N.Y. Report Number 3., August 1, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Frederick P. Clarke and Associates, 1 inserted map.
    - Planning Notes for the Clients of Frederick P. Clarke and Associates, November 1, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Land Use, Zoning, and Economic Analysis (New Rochelle, N.Y.), January 1, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      New Rochelle Planning Board
  - Land Use - U.S.- New York (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - General Land Use. Syracuse Housing Authority., July 15, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      The Syracuse Housing Authority
    - Memorandum. Allocation of Industrial Areas in the City (Syracuse, N.Y.), September 3, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      T.W. Mackesey
    - Report on the Master Plan of Land Use Proposed By the City Planning Commission (New York, N.Y.), December 3, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Report No. 4 - Land Use and Zoning. Proposed Zoning Ordinance. (Utica, N.Y.), May 1, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Harland Bartholomew & Associates, City Planning Board of Utica, N.Y.
  - Land Use - U.S.- New York (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Land Use Survey and Analysis. Victor, N.Y., May 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Town of Victor Planning Board, Arthur Reed
    - Land Use and Local Finance., December 1, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Westchester County Commission on Government
    - Rochester, N.Y. Land Use Map, January 1, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Land Use - U.S. - New York (Oversized), 1948 (Box 61)
  - Land Use - U.S.- North Carolina (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - A Land Development Plan for Raleigh, March 1, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Department of Planning, Raleigh, N.C.
  - Land Use - U.S.- Ohio (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Land Use Planning Committee Annual Report 1962., January 1, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Development Committee for Greater Columbus
    - Land Use Plan. Butler County, Ohio., January 1, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Ladislas Segoe and Associates
  - Land Use - U.S.- Oklahoma (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Metropolitan Tulsa Preliminary Land Use Plan., January 1, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Tulsa Metropolitan Area Planning Commission.
  - Land Use - U.S.- Oregon (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Land Use. Forest Grove., April 1, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Forest Grove City Planning Commission.
    - Problems and Institutional Factors Affecting Land Use in a Northwest County., June 1, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Melvin L. Upchurch, U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Agricultural Economics
  - Land Use - U.S.- Oregon (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Empire Oregon. Land Use and Traffic Plan., July 1, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Empire City Planning Commission
    - Land Use Inventory Procedure Manual, May 1, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Mid Willamette Valley Council of Governments
  - Land Use - U.S.- Rhode Island (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Non Urban Land. Present Use and Economic Classification., September 1, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Rhode Island Development Council, Planning Division, 2 maps inserted.
  - Land Use - U.S.- Rhode Island (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Land Use Comparison. 1946-1953., January 1, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Providence R.I. City Plan Commission
  - Land Use - U.S.- Tennessee (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Murfreesboro Future Land Use Plan., December 1, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      Murfreesboro Regional Planning Commission
    - Murfreesboro Land Use Survey and Analysis., December 1, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Land Use - U.S.- Tennessee (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Land Use Analysis. (Knoxville and Knox County, Tennessee), June 1, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Metropolitan Planning Commission, Knoxville and Knox County, Tennessee
  - Land Use - U.S.- Tennessee (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Land Use Plan. (Knoxville and Knox County, Tennessee), June 1, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      Metropolitan Planning Commission, Knoxville and Knox County, Tennessee, 1 map inserted.
  - Land Use - U.S.- Tennessee (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Tennessee Major Land Use Problems., March 1, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      Tennessee State Planning Commission.
    - A Guide to Community Growth. General Land Use Plan. Johnson City, Tennessee (Box 1, Folder 23)
      Johnson City Local Planning Assistance Division.
  - Land Use - U.S.- Tennessee (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - The Use of Land In Kingsport, July 1, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Kingsport Planning Commission
    - Dyersburg Land Use Plan., July 1, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Dyersburg Planning Commission
    - Newbern, Tennessee Land Use Plan., January 1, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      The Newbern Municipal Regional Planning Commission
    - Newbern Land Use Survey and Analysis, November 1, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Land Use - U.S.- Vermont (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Land Utilization as a Basis of Rural Economic Organization. Based on a Study of Land Utilization and Related Problems in 13 Hill Towns of Vermont, June 1, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      C.F. Clayton, L.J. Peet, University of Vermont and State Agricultural College, Vermont Agricultural Experiment Station
  - Land Use - U.S.- Virginia (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Land Uses-1953- Fairfax County, Virginia., October 1, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      Francis Dodd McHugh
  - Land Use - U.S. - Virginia (Oversized), 1959 (Box 71)
  - Land Use - U.S.- Washington (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Land Use (Spokane, Washington), April 1, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      City Plan Commission, Spokane, Washington.
  - Land Use - U.S.- Washington (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Generalized Land Use Plan. A Part of the Comprehensive Plan. (Tacoma, Washington), January 1, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      City Planning Commission, Tacoma, Washington
    - Land Use and Zoning. A Part of the Tacoma Master Plan., September 1, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Land Use - U.S.- Washington (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Vancouver, Washington. Adopted Comprehensive Residential Land Use Plan., August 1, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      City of Vancouver, Washington Planning Office. 2 copies.
  - Land Use - U.S. - Washington (Oversized), 1943 (Box 61)
  - Land Use - U.S.- Wisconsin (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Land Use Planning In the Metropolitan Milwaukee Area, May 23, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      Metropolitan Study Commission Committee on Land Use and Zoning
    - A Complete Land Use Survey. (Oshkosh, Wisconsin), July 1, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Land Use - Foreign- Canada (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Geographical Factors and Land Use In Toronto., August 1, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      Nadine A. H. Deacon, Canadian Geographical Journal
    - The Niagara Area. Changing Land Uses., July 1, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      Ontario Department of Municipal Affairs. Community Planning Branch.
  - Land Use - Foreign- Great Britain (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - The Concepts of Land Use Planning. Aerial Photography and Photo-Interpretation. Land Classification for Land Use Planning. Systematic Approach to Land Use Planning. Provisional Procedures for Ranch Planning., ca. 1950 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - The Control of Land Use., June 1, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      Minister of Town and Country Planning and the Secretary of State of Scotland.
  - Land Use - Foreign- Greece (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Report on a Sample Survey of Land Use in Greece, May 1, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      National Statistical Service of Greece
  - Land Use - Foreign- Latin America (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Problems and Techniques of Land Use Control In Latin American Cities, November 1, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      Francis Violich, published in Servicios Publicos
  - Land - Values (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Land Values in Relation to Planning and Housing in the United States, February 1, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Sir Raymond Unwin, reprinted from the Journal of Land Pubic Utility Economics, Vol. 37, No. 1
    - Urban Disintegration and the Future of Land Investments, November 1, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Gordon Whitnall, reprinted from the Journal of Land Pubic Utility Economics, Vol. 17, No. 4, pp. 440-451.
    - Regional Planning and Its Effect on Values, October 30, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Ernest J. Bohn, Regional Association of Cleveland
    - The Valuation of Land In Urban Blighted Areas, July 1, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Homer Hoyt, Leonard C. Smith, The Appraisal Journal,
    - Valuation Problems Involving Reuse of Urban Land. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Downtown- the Appraiser's Dilemma and the Assessor's Nightmare (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Nathan Nirenstein, 72nd Annual Conference of the Association of Massachusetts
  - Land - Values (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Mortgage Status of Farm Land In South Dakota., January 1, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      South Dakota State Planning Board
    - Relationship of Price and Assessed Value of Real Estate Sold In Philadelphia, 1943-1948, August 1, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Philadelphia City Planning Comission, Public Information Bulletin No. 3
    - Modern Appraisal Techniques Applied to the Equalization Program - Cuyahoga County, Ohio, 1954 - 1958., January 1, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      John J. Carney, County Auditor
  - Land Subdivision
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Alabama (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Arkansas, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - California, 1940-1960 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Connecticut, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Illinois, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Kansas, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Kentucky, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Louisiana (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Maine, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Maryland (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Massachusetts, 1950-1960 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Michigan, 1930,1950 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Minnesota, 1940,1960 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Mississippi, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Nevada (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Hamshire, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - New Jersey, 1930-1960 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - New Mexico (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - New York, 1950-1960 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Ohio, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Oklahoma, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Oregon (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Tennessee (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Texas, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Land Subdivision - U.S. - Wisconsin, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Land Subdivision - Foreign - Canada, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Land Subdivision - Ordinances - General, 1930,1950 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Land - Subdivision Ordinances
      - Land - Subdivision Ordinances - U.S. - Alabama, 1940-1950 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Land - Subdivision Ordinances - U.S. - Arizona (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Land - Subdivision Ordinances - U.S. - California, 1940-1960 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Land - Subdivision Ordinances - U.S. - California, 1940-1950 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Land - Subdivision Ordinances - U.S. - Connecticut, 1940-1950 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Land - Subdivision Ordinances - U.S. - Colorado (Box 19, Folder 17)